<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Resilient Communities</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Resilient Communities</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Facilitate a Zoom Workshop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-facilitate-a-zoom-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/how-to-facilitate-a-zoom-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Today, our world is more interconnected than ever before. This means that no matter where we are physically located, we will most likely be able to communicate with other people in various places. We live in a world where people can work and learn anywhere, as long as they have access to the internet. This means that I can live in the United States, go to school in a different state than I currently live in, and complete an international internship in Morocco, which is exactly what I have done this semester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rees Interviews Eastman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/rees-interviews-eastman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/rees-interviews-eastman/</guid>
      <description>Rees: We both came to Morocco through the Peace Corps in 2014. What motivated you to join?&#xA;Eastman: I was finishing my undergrad in 2012, and at that time the American economy wasn’t too great. I saw people getting out of their BA and not even getting planning jobs. I started doing classes with Coverdell fellows in the MA program, and I started talking with them. I was laying in my bed late one night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Workshop Interview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-workshop-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-workshop-interview/</guid>
      <description>Antoinette: What is the first workshop you conducted?&#xA;Rees: Maybe in 2015 I was in the peace corps, and I led a workshop called a needs-based assessment with an African corps volunteer, named Sufian. It was in Rabat or Casablanca; I can’t remember which one. I think it was in Rabat, He and I basically travelled all around Morocco, giving this needs-based assessment workshop. The funny thing is originally I was not supposed to do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/less-is-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/less-is-more/</guid>
      <description>Challenges as an International Intern&#xA;For part 1 of phase 1, I was in charge of helping Mr. Eastman with the Green Climate Fund (GCF) project. As I was not loaded with any heavy tasks, I tried to research some things about the project and that consumed a considerable amount of time. Maybe an hour of one-on-ones is enough for some, but the project at hand probably needs more time to understand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Your Time!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/manage-your-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/manage-your-time/</guid>
      <description>Initial Challenges&#xA;When I first started as a part-time planning intern at RC, I was aware of the fact that the largest obstacle to my internship will involve time management. Thus, as an international graduate student studying and working remotely, I was strategically planning my schedule for a remote working environment. Despite these measures, I had few challenges towards the start due to my commitment to multiple works in order to achieve the required hours of the co-op semester.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
